<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<root>
  <str key="99324390-ugdt" type="ugdt" originalKey="99324390">Camo-Net Bumper Kit</str>
  <str key="166462093-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="166462093">Completionist</str>
  <str key="351420902-ugdt" type="ugdt" originalKey="351420902">Camo-Net Hubcaps</str>
  <str key="634773111-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="634773111">Conduit Repositories are the attacker's destination for stolen Conduits in any facility using the Capture the Conduit mechanic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Repositories must be hacked by the attacking faction for their carriers to deposit Conduits.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The facility gains a single Strike when an attacker deposits their Conduit. A facility requires a set number of Strikes for it to be captured by an attacking faction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If there are multiple attackers, the faction that scores the final Strike will capture the facility.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Strike will be removed from a facility if a Conduit has not been deposited in 3 minutes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defenders secure the facility if the number of Strikes drops to zero or once all Repositories have been recaptured (and no Conduits are currently away from their Podiums).</str>
  <str key="854871882-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="854871882">Title: Completionist</str>
  <str key="1711042064-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="1711042064">Camo-Net Bumper Kit</str>
  <str key="1748369680-ugdt" type="ugdt" originalKey="1748369680">Camo-Net Exterior Kit</str>
  <str key="1793430989-ugdt" type="ugdt" originalKey="1793430989">Title: Huggable</str>
  <str key="1881665639-ugdt" type="ugdt" originalKey="1881665639">Sugar Tile Camo</str>
  <str key="1953791354-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="1953791354">Dig deep with this combat-ready trench shovel. All factions can use this weapon.</str>
  <str key="2029058942-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="2029058942">Sugar Tile Camo</str>
  <str key="2132312554-ugdt" type="ugdt" originalKey="2132312554">Trench Shovel</str>
  <str key="2323858269-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="2323858269">Conduit Podiums are the starting locations for Conduits in any facility using the Capture the Conduit mechanic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attackers must transport the Conduit to any of that base's Conduit Repositories to score a Strike toward capturing that base.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attacking non-MAX infantry class can interact with any Conduit Podium that contains a Conduit. Doing so will pick up and carry that Conduit, refilling the carrier's personal shields as well as providing a temporary increase in sprint speed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Conduit prevents its carrier from using any equipment other than their class ability, although the thrust of the Light Assault's Ambusher Jump Jets is greatly reduced. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Conduit can be away from its Podium for up to two minutes, the remaining time for which can be seen by the carrier. After this timer has expired the Conduit will automatically be returned to its Podium.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Being killed or switching to a different equipment slot will cause the Conduit to be dropped. Infantry that has held the Conduit and dropped it will be unable to pick it back up again for several seconds. If a defender picks up a dropped Conduit, it will be instantly returned to its Podium.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conduits that have been returned to their podiums through capture, expired timer, or defender pickup cannot be picked up again until a cooldown period has expired.</str>
  <str key="2468640562-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="2468640562">Camo-Net Exterior Kit</str>
  <str key="2642564166-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="2642564166">Trench Shovel</str>
  <str key="2733315999-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="2733315999">Camo-Net Windshield Kit</str>
  <str key="2766124846-ugdt" type="ugdt" originalKey="2766124846">Camo-Net Windshield Kit</str>
  <str key="3062693019-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="3062693019">Title: Huggable</str>
  <str key="3206499038-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="3206499038">Huggable</str>
  <str key="3235265012-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="3235265012">Camo-Net Lumifiber Trim</str>
  <str key="3913851876-ugdt" type="ugdt" originalKey="3913851876">Title: Completionist</str>
  <str key="4039028107-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="4039028107">Camo-Net Hubcaps</str>
  <str key="4051703269-ucdt" type="ucdt" originalKey="4051703269">Prime Convoy Bundle</str>
</root>
